仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
翻译:  冰蓝   洗七里   glida
翻译:  吃货丁小七    猪肉白菜水饺
校对:  主席请选赛太公
时间轴:  三水
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第三集
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
手机APP搜索
人人影视字幕组
一键收藏网盘资源生活大爆炸 吸血鬼日记
西部世界 谍网 超女
美剧资源应有尽有
扫码即刻关注
Zimuzu特别推荐
马上关注微信人人美剧（rrmjapp）
真高兴你喜欢那栋房子  有几件事跟你说说
I'm so glad you like the house! Hey, so a few things --
一  所有家电都包括在内
One, all the appliances are included,
二  之前的住户在屋里被杀害了
two, the previous residents were murdered there,
三  房子刚通过霉菌检查
and three, it just passed mold inspection.
我们什么时候
So, when should we --
好  我懂
Yeah. I get it.
我们继续看吧
Well, we'll -- we'll just keep looking.
但这给了房子鲜明的特色啊
Although it does give the house character.
如果那些墙能说话就好了
If those walls could talk.
我同意  不好笑  再见
I agree. It's not funny. Bye-bye.
没事  亲爱的  你能卖掉那栋凶宅的
It's okay, honey. You're gonna sell that murder house.
谢谢
Thanks.
把血迹从我身上弄走
"Ahh, Get this blood off me!"
什么  从谁身上
What? Wh-- Off who?
墙[沃尔一家]
The Walls.
巴布和撒德·沃尔吗  他们惹到什么麻烦吗
You mean Barb and Thad Wall? Are they in trouble?
遵照医嘱  两天不能说话
喉咙很痛  传染性单核细胞增多症很严重
作为这个家庭里唯一有槽要吐的人
我却不能说话
早上好
Morning.
你想来点咖啡吗
Oh, would you like some coffee?
天啊不要  我整晚没睡  我得去睡觉了
God, no. I've been up all night. I got to get to bed.
你们能别用搅拌机
Hey, can you guys not use, like, the blender
吸尘器什么的吗
or vacuum or anything?
我需要清静五个小时
I just need five hours.
看来你不停止找新工作了
So, I guess we've stopped looking for a new job?
实际上  是的
Actually, we have.
你女儿自己创业了
Your daughter has gone into business for herself.
太棒了  什么业务
Great. What kind of business?
我召集了一群姑娘
I put a group of girls together,
我们通过社交媒体宣传俱乐部和别的东西
and we promote clubs and stuff via social media.
听起来不像是靠谱工作
That doesn't sound like a real job.
你的上一份工作听起来都不怎么靠谱了
Your last job barely sounded like a real job.
我们昨晚宣传水烟吧赚了五百块呢
We made $500 last night for promoting a hookah bar.
我还记得你小的时候
I remember when you were a little girl.
你跟我说你希望你的工作是"公主"
You told me you wanted your job to be "Princess."
真想回到那些日子
I would kill for those days.
所以你才穿得像是个水烟[妓女]吗
"Is that why you're dressed like a hookah?"
亲爱的  你又在说听不懂的话了
Honey, you're not making sense again.
你需要躺下休息吗
Do you need to lie down?
妈妈  我就知道你会这样
Mom, I knew you would be like this.
爸爸  你能理解我的事业  对吧
Dad, you understand what I'm doing, right?
当然啦  社交媒体的力量
Of course. Power of social media.
我是"懂你"战队的人
I'm on "Team Gets It."
你们能不能给我个机会
Can you guys just give me a chance
让我带这事业起步
to get this thing off the ground?
当然可以
Yes. We can.
我总是保持开明的态度
I always keep an open mind.
行  这事你负责  我太忙没空
Fine. You take this one. My plate's full.
我今天要去学校面谈
I've got a meeting at school today
谈论卢克上大学有何选择
to discuss Luke's college options.
那估计几句就谈完了
Should be a short meeting.
快扔  快扔
Throw it, baby! Throw it!
好棒
Yes!
德怀特  横向传球就是这样理解的
Dwight, that's the way you read the reverse.
各位  围过来
Gentlemen, circle up!
我们3比0了  但如果我们要获得冠军
We are 3-0, but if we're gonna go all the way,
我们都需要像德怀特一样
we all need to be as mentally
内心坚强  体格健壮
and physically tough as Dwight.
-教练  -怎么了
- Coach? - Yes?
你知道我爸爸在军队服役吧
You know my dad's in the service?
他被重新分配到了佛罗里达州
He's being restationed to Florida.
什么
What?
今天是我的最后一天
Today's my last day.
好吧
Okay, uh...
大家喝点水
everybody get some water.
-教练  你没事吧  -没事
- Coach, you okay? - Mm-hmm. Yeah.
欢迎啊
Welcome, welcome!
-你好  -我们开始可以吗
- Hello! - Shall we start?
不等卢克的辅导员了吗
Shouldn't we wait for Luke's guidance counselor?
马克斯老师正经历一场惨烈的离婚
Mrs. Marks is going through a terrible divorce.
她现在很脆弱
She's very fragile right now.
所以我尽量不让她处理比较有挑战性的事情
So I'm trying to keep the more challenging cases away from her.
我幼小心灵没受伤
None taken.
我仔细查看了你的成绩单
I have been perusing your transcript.
随口说句
And, uh, apropos of nothing --
不是每个孩子都注定要上大学的
You know, not every kid is destined for college.
但卢克是  对吧
But Luke is, right?
好吧  我配合演出
Okay, I'll play along.
现实是  卢克的成绩和分数
The reality is that Luke's grades and test scores
是我们教育者所称的差强人意
are what we educators call suboptimal.
那是好事吗
Is that good?
明白我的意思了吧
See what I'm talking about?
所以我们得专注靠
So, we're gonna have to really juice
课外活动加分  好吗
the extracurriculars, okay?
他对什么比较感兴趣
Is there anything he's, uh, passionate about?
我爱鸡肉馅饼
I love chicken pot pie.
记得我说过主要由我来说话吗
Remember when I said I would do most of the talking?
布朗校长
Principal Brown!
我是《每日海豚报》的莱斯丽·关·柯林斯
Leslie Kwan Collins from The Daily Dolphin.
我知道你是谁  莱斯丽
Yeah. I know who you are, Leslie.
我们每次都要来一遍吗
Must we do this dance every single time?
你想对埃里克·汤普森突然辞职
Would you like to issue a statement about Eric Thompson's
学生会主席一事发表声明吗
abrupt resignation as Student Council President?
行啊  这是我的声明  呸
Sure. Here's my statement -- Pbht!
我的线人说他被抓到
My sources say that he was caught selling
在分类广告网上倒卖学校的萨克斯管
school saxophones on Craigslist.
看来可以写有"萨"[性]丑闻啊
Well, guess you could say you had a "Sax" Scandal, then.
"萨"丑闻  我要用这个标题
A sax scandal -- I'm running with that.
谢谢你全家  很有帮助
Oh, thanks a lot for that. Very helpful.
说到哪里来了
So, where did we land?
是让卢克吃阿得拉还是怎么  我忘了
We're putting Luke on Adderall or taking him off? I forget.
一种治疗注意力缺失或者多动症的药  不宜乱吃
有学生吃了来增加专注力  又被成为"聪明药"
我们根本没在讨论阿得拉
We weren't discussing Adderall.
但阿得拉的确帮助了很多孩子呢
Although, Adderall has helped a lot of kids.
我们需要一个新主席  我为何不去竞选呢
Hey, we need a new president. Why don't I just do that?
也许会很酷
Maybe it'll be cool.
我的确喜欢指挥人
I do like bossing people around.
那叫领导能力
That's called leadership.
瞧瞧你
Wow, look at you.
我觉得我在变成熟呢
I think I'm maturing.
卢克  这责任十分重大
Luke, this is a lot of work.
你确定你能胜任吗
Are you sure you're up for it?
妈妈  这是我一分钟前听到后
Mom, it's all I've ever wanted
唯一想要的东西
since I heard about it a minute ago.
好吧  我觉得你该去竞选
Yeah. Well, I think you should go for it.
我想不出一个理由来反对
I can't think of a single reason why not.
曼尼竞选主席
好  姑娘们
All right, girls.
关于昨晚我有些想说的
So, I have a couple notes about last night.
亚利桑那  我看了你的自拍
Arizona, I was looking at your selfies.
-你爸妈是绿头鸭吗  -什么
- Are your parents mallards? - What?
你那鸭脸是怎么回事
What's with all the duckface?
你看起来就像在参加水边的单身派对
You look like you're at a bachelorette party in Tampa.
而你  卡滕  我竟然看到你在
And, Katen, did I see you drinking a water
"红房"酒吧里喝水
at The Red Room?
我隔天早上需要早起
I had to wake up early in the morning.
是啊  这正是我们想宣传的
Oh, yes, because that's what we're promoting --
一间能让人做出理智决定的酒吧
a club where people make good decisions.
对不起
I'm sorry!
你弱爆了
You are so weak.
真不敢相信我竟然让你在湖人队面前亲我
I can't believe I let you kiss me in front of the Lakers.
我不想学卡滕说话
Not to sound like a total Katen,
可海莉的新工作看起来不怎么样啊
but Haley's new job seems whack.
如果海莉想学宣传推广
If Haley wants to work in promotion,
她该跟我的人学学  梅尔夫·舍希特尔先生
she should learn from my guy -- Mr. Merv Schechter.
他无数伟大的创新发明里包含了
Among his brilliant innovations --
在篮球比赛中散发折扣劵的室内飞艇
the indoor blimp that drops coupons at basketball games.
可惜  那发明后来
Sadly, it was later weaponized
被一些恐怖分子组织装备上了武器
by several terrorist organizations.
杰  你需要把什么蔬菜切丝吗
Hey, Jay, do you need to julienne any vegetables?
-啥  -如果需要  你可以用
- What? - If so, you can use the knife
你外孙在我背上插的那把刀来切丝
your grandson jammed in my back.
那倒值得我一试
Well, that was worth the journey.
发生什么事了  宝贝
What happened, papi?
卢克打算参选
Luke decided to run against me
跟我竞争学生会主席宝座
for Student Council President.
我把人生献给了公共服务事业
I've devoted my entire life to public service,
现在却要受到一个把人生献给了
only to be challenged by a guy who's devoted his entire life
看网上摔滑板视频的人的挑战
to watching skateboard fails on YouTube.
卢克要竞选学生会主席吗
Luke's running for President?
我是说  我爱他  但是...
I mean, I love him, but --
杰说得对  卢克是个蠢货
Jay is right. Luke is a dummy.
我可没这么说过
Never said that.
他想要战  那便战吧
He wants a fight, he's got one.
我要用语言给我的继侄子
I'm going to hit my step-nephew
一点颜色看看
with so many stinging rejoinders
然后他就会哭给他继舅舅看
that he'll be crying step-uncle.
真棒  激情嘴仗
Yes! Dynamic wordplay!
高中的孩子最爱看了
High-school kids love that!
-他输定了  -不一定
- He's gonna lose. - He might not.
你真的想赌运气吗
Really, you want to roll those dice? Hmm.
还记得他上次竞选输了有多抑郁吗
Remember how depressed he got when he lost the last election?
爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
我们的小女孩在这啊
There she is -- our little girl!
米奇尔  你还记得她来我们家之前
Mitchell, do you remember back before we had her
我们是怎么担心家里多一个人
how we were so worried that an extra person
是不是会太挤吗
would make the house feel so crowded?
不  我不记得我们有担心过
Uh... no. I don't remember that at all.
我们错了
Oh, boy, were we wrong.
-你当初不想要我吗  -宝贝  这事跟你没关系
- You didn't want me? - This isn't about you, honey.
我猜你大爸有所图谋
I think Daddy's ramping up to something.
总之  橄榄球队有一名队员
Anyhoo, there's a football player on the team
需要找个地方住到赛...
who needs a place to stay until the end of football --
不  不  不行
No. No, no, no.
-能让我说完吗  -好  你说吧
- Would you let me finish? - Okay, fine. Go ahead.
季结束
Season.
不  他不能住这里
No. He can't stay here.
小卡  我们没有多的房间
Cam, we don't have the room.
他可以睡书房
He can sleep in the den.
我爱书房  我在书房里看电视
I love the den. I watch TV in the den.
另外  我们现在吵架之后你今晚睡哪里
Besides, where are you gonna sleep tonight after this fight?
他可以住楼上的公寓
He can sleep in the apartment upstairs?
不  我们需要租金来还贷款
No. We need the rent to pay the mortgage.
抱歉  小卡  这事没得商量
I'm sorry, Cam. It's not gonna happen.
教练  我能进来了吗
Coach, can I come in yet?
看  你现在害我陷入一个很尴尬的局面
See, now you've put me in an awkward position.
他为什么不能跟别人一起住
Why can't he stay with someone else?
因为我是他橄榄球教练而他父亲信任我
Because I'm his football coach, and his father trusts me.
小卡  你为什么总是...
Cam, why you always --
-你好  -你好
- Hey! - Hey!
-你好  -好啊
- Hi. - Hey.
你为什么每次做这种重大决定之前
Why do you always insist on making these big decisions
都不先跟我讨论一下
without discussing it with me first?
-我哪有  -你邀请我们
- I do not. - You asked that couple
在租车行碰见的那对夫妻跟我们一起度假
we met at the car-rental counter to vacation with us.
不邀请感觉很没礼貌啊
It would have been rude not to.
可那是我们的蜜月之旅啊
It was our honeymoon.
-抱歉  -门把手掉了
- Sorry, your... - doorknob came off.
-当然啦  大个子  -又掉啦
- It sure did, big guy! - Again?
好吧  那没关系
Okay, that's fine.
我已经有点受不了了
I'm already hating this.
我不想显得在嫌弃你
I don't want to be critical.
你不是吧
You got to be kidding me.
但这个特质是你比较不讨喜的一个
This is not one of your more loveable traits.
-什么特质  -就总是先拒绝一切
- What isn't? - Always saying "No" to things
虽然最终总会想通
and then eventually coming around.
我们为什么不能跳过不讨喜的部分呢
Why can't we just skip to the good part?
我觉得如果做这种单方面决定的人是我
I think you'd have a different attitude about this
你的态度肯定会不一样
if I was the one constantly making unilateral decisions.
如果是对你很重要的东西  我会支持你的
If it was something important to you, I would support it.
你真的确定吗
Oh. Are you sure about that?
百分之百  而且当你逐渐了解德怀特到
100%, and once you get to know Dwight the way...
像我一样了解他  你会发现他会增加...
I do, you will find that he will enrich --
好了  德怀特  快停止一切动作
Okay, Dwight, please stop moving.
你好  卢克
Hola, Luke!
你们来我屋里想做什么
Hey, guys. What are you doing in my room?
就想来看看我最喜欢的外孙
Just wanted to see my favorite grandson.
你们喝酒了吧
You guys been drinking?
量跟平常都差不多
No more than usual.
我听到一个传闻
I heard a rumor that you're running
说你要竞选学生会主席
for Student Council President.
是的  我正在写我的演讲稿
Yep. I'm working on my speech right now.
好吧
Good.
要我我肯定不想卷入这破事儿
I know I wouldn't want any part of that nonsense.
我也不想  这事不够性感
Me either -- not very sexy.
这需要花费很多时间  甚至导致你
It takes so much time and then you wouldn't
连骑你的迷你单车的机会都没有
even have a chance to ride your mini-bike.
我没有迷你单车
I don't have a mini-bike.
还没有  但如果你能够配合...
Yet. But if you play ball...
卢克
Hey, Luke,
你得帮我去...
I need you to take the --
你们在这里干什么呢
What are you guys doing in here?
他们想贿赂我不要去竞选主席
They're trying to bribe me not to run for president.
什么
What?
曼尼多年来努力想当上学生会主席
Manny has been working all his life to be president,
现在卢克大摇大摆横插一脚
and now Luke just salsas in
想夺了曼尼的主席地位
and tries to take it away from him.
这不公平
It's not fair.
听着  这对卢克也很重要
Look, this means a lot to Luke, too.
这给他全新的目标感
It's given him a whole new sense of purpose.
我听够了  我心意已决
I've heard enough, and I've made my decision.
曼尼这学期当主席
Manny will be president this term,
明年我们再帮卢克竞选
and we'll run Luke next year.
我就要毕业了
I'm graduating.
就是这种精神
That's the spirit!
我不想来这一招
I don't like to play this card,
但我是大家长  我发话了
but I am the patriarch, and I have spoken.
这招行不通  老爸  因为我懒得鸟你
Not much of a card, Dad, 'cause I don't really care.
不如你们两个快点离开
So, how about the two of you get going,
因为卢克要准备发言稿了
because Luke has a speech to work on?
你想跟普里契特家的政治机器对着干
You want to go up against the Pritchett political machine?
就这么着吧
So be it.
-再见  外公  -再见  孩子
- Bye, Grandpa! - Bye, kiddo!
卢克  我们需要谈谈
All right, Luke, we need to talk.
外公要冲你来了
Grandpa is coming for you,
他可是曾成功助人赢得竞选
and he has run successful political campaigns before.
他在同性恋还被歧视时
He got Mitchell elected class president
就让米奇尔当选班长
before it was cool to be gay.
我能行的  老妈
I've got this, Mom.
我会在炮台上竞选
I'm running on a gun platform.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我在说  我这两管大炮
I'm talking about... my guns.
好了  来看看你的发言稿
All right, let's look at the speech.
我觉得相当好
I think it's pretty good.
我开场先开布朗校长那几个孩子
I'm opening with a joke about how Principal Brown's kids
看着都像邮递员的玩笑
look like the mailman.
全选  删除
And select all, delete.
我必须做自己
Hey! I got to be me.
不  你必须不像自己
No, you got to be less you.
如果你想赢  就要比曼尼更曼尼
If you want this, you got to out-Manny Manny.
艾丽克斯毕业时我给你买的西服呢
Oh! Where's that suit I got you for Alex's graduation?
都过一年了
That was a year ago.
我现在穿不上了
I can't fit into that anymore,
因为我的两管大...
because of my gu--
知道了  别说了
I know, I got it.
这本来是满的
This was full.
对不起
Sorry.
你会失望的
You're just gonna be disappointed.
大家早上好啊
Good morning, everyone.
如果你饿了  我在烤面包机后藏了几块饼干
If you're hungry, I hid some cookies behind the toaster.
被我找到了
I found them.
我想了想你昨天说的话
Oh, I was thinking about what you said yesterday,
你说得对
and you were right.
我们应该能自己做决定
We should be able to make our own decisions, you know?
我只能说  再次谢谢你
Ay, all I can say is, thank you again.
戴恩·艾德娜  跟你的养父们问好
Dane Edna, say hi to your foster daddies.
罗纳多  这是什么情况
Ronaldo, what's going on?
我们要在罗纳多带胡娇
Oh, we're taking care of Dane Edna
去亚洲做手术期间照顾戴恩·艾德娜
while Ronaldo takes Pepper to Asia for a medical procedure.
他没事
Is everything okay?
别担心
Oh, don't worry.
别说出去  他要去老挝做个下巴沟
Between us, he's getting a monkey chin in Laos.
所以这个月大家都有乐子
Oh, so it's a fun month for everyone, huh?
我会想念这个美丽天后的
Mm, I'm going to miss this beautiful diva.
她的胃有点挑剔
Her tummy can get a little fussy,
所以如果你们不确定该给她做什么吃
so if you're ever wondering what to cook for her,
问问自己"帕蒂·卢波恩会吃什么"
just ask yourself, "What would Patti LuPone eat?"
知名百老汇老牌女明星
抱歉  我没问你的意见
Oh, I'm sorry. I-I didn't ask you about this,
但这真的对我很重要
but it's really important to me.
你也说过会支持我的任何决定
And you said you'd support any decision I made.
我不知道你在做什么
I'm not sure what you're doing,
因为你如此难以捉摸
because you're being so subtle,
但如果你觉得这个家里需要
but if you think a giant, slobbery dog
一条流着口水的大狗  那么我绝对配合
is what this household needs, then color me gung ho.
这是她的药
Here are her medicines.
-箔纸包装的是从菊花塞  -好
- The ones wrapped in foil don't go in the mouth. - Okay.
对了  我很抱歉
Ah, yeah. I'm so sorry.
我们训练她要把碳水化合物带离我们身边
We've trained her to take carbs away from us.
我无法理解
I don't get it.
你看着超棒  我爱极了
You look amazing. I love it!
你为什么给我买这身衣服
Why did you buy this for me?
因为我觉得你在台上演讲时
'Cause I thought you would look great up there
穿这套会很帅
when you give your big speech.
我在竞选主席  老妈  我要穿西服打领带
I'm running for president, Mom. I'll wear a suit and tie.
那你就可以直接穿去自己的葬礼了
Well, then you'll be dressed for your funeral.
孩子  你得了解你的观众
Kid, you got to know your audience.
你不认为我能和同龄人有共鸣啊
You don't think I can relate to my peers?
那这下真是完了个蛋
Well, this is a fine kettle of fish.
我会尽可能温柔地说
I'm gonna say this as gently as I know how...
你会输掉
You're going to lose!
我没打算吼出来  但至少你知道了
Well, I wasn't gonna yell it, but at least it's out there.
等等  你觉得我会输
Wait. You think I'm going to lose?
但你从未觉得我会输过
But you never think I'm going to lose!
听着  你是个好孩子
Look, you're a great kid.
我们只是想说多点便装星期五风
All we're saying is be a little more Casual Friday,
少点圣灰星期三[基督教大斋首日]风
a little less Ash Wednesday.
是啊  走上台说些
Yeah. Go up there and be like,
"你们好啊  牛逼兄弟们"
"Yo! What's up, ballers?!"
"星期一放假  去吃点披萨什么的"
"Mondays off. Like, pizza and whatever."
感觉有点奇怪
This is feeling a little weird.
相信我们
Trust us.
你们觉得有用我就听话
If you really think it'll help.
趁着没忘  把披萨饼的事记下来
Hey, write that pizza-pie thing down while it's fresh.
希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind.
我同意他们在房子里玩取物游戏
I decided it was fine if they played fetch in the house.
没问题  我支持这个决定
Not at all. I support that decision.
我真期待接下来会发生什么
Well, I look forward to what's about to happen.
-好吧  -取到了
- Okay. - There we are.
-好了  -很好
- All right. - Nice.
我出发了  教练  比赛见
Okay, Coach. I'll meet you at the game.
好  谁是冠军
Yes! Who's a winner?
-我是冠军  -谁是冠军
- I'm a winner! - Who's a winner?!
我是冠军
I'm a winner!!
老天
Oh, my...
好吧  我先说
Okay. I'm gonna go first.
我小心眼  故意报复
I was petty and vindictive,
我会找别人照顾这条狗
and I will find someone else to look after the dog.
你有要说的吗
Do you have anything to say?
谢谢你  我知道让你说这话有多不容易
Thank you. I know that couldn't have been easy.
小卡  我对天发誓
Cam, I swear to God --
好好  你说的对
Okay, okay. You're right.
我应该先跟你商量的
I should have consulted you first.
今晚的比赛结束后
I'll tell Dwight that he has to move out
我会告诉德怀特他必须搬出去
after the game tonight.
谢谢你
Thank you.
虽然你们不在乎  但还是说一声
Not that anybody cares, but for lunch,
我午饭只吃到一粒润喉糖
I had a lozenge.
这事多久能办完
So, uh, how long is this going to take?
我只是需要再订一些宣传用的飞盘
I just need to reorder some promotional Frisbees,
顺便和梅尔夫打声招呼
and say a quick hi to Merv,
这位天才在过去十多年里
the genius who supplied me with coasters
一直帮我做杯垫和钥匙链
and key chains for over a decade.
他甚至还把我的脸印在枕头上呢
He even put my face on a pillow.
这个故事让我想找个枕头来闷死自己
That story makes me want to put a pillow over my face.
咱速战速决行吗  我四点还得去做美黑
Can we just get this over with? I have a spray tan at 4:00.
美黑  谁需要做美黑
Spray tan! Who needs a spray tan?
冬天没得晒太阳的人需要
Someone in winter.
所以美黑优惠劵就得跟冰铲配
That's why you put a coupon on a ice scraper.
厉害吧  又挣够钱送我一个孙子去好大学
Boom! Just sent another grandkid to Brandeis.
他一出手  就是正中红心
He shoots, he scores!
你能相信这位青年才俊的孙子都上大学了吗
Can you believe this young man has a grandkid in college?
年轻与否都是由生活方式决定的
Mm! It's all about lifestyle.
真的  我每天健走八公里
Really, I walk five miles a day,
还做过一大堆整形手术
and I've had a tremendous amount of plastic surgery.
关于你那幢急于卖出去的房产
Oh! I had a brainstorm on that property of yours
我脑力激荡了一番
that you're trying to unload.
就是死过人那幢
You know, where the people -- Ckkk!
是啊
Yeah.
你把它当成卖点
You lean into it. Hmm?
你叫它"大屠杀庄园"
You-You call it "Massacre Manor,"
"唐顿墓园"
"Downton Stabby,"
"杀人魔曼森[大宅]"
"Charles Mansion."
类似的双关梗我能想出无数个
I mean, like, I-I got a million of them.
其实大概还能想出仨
Actually, I probably -- I have three more.
瞧见没  大师
See? A master.
梅尔夫  这是我女儿海莉
Aww. Merv, meet my daughter Haley.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
你爸告诉我
Your daddy tells me
你被麦德逊大道[广告业]的热情感染了
that you have come down with the Madison Avenue flu.
他说的话我一个字都听不懂
I don't understand anything that's happening here.
我看《嘻哈帝国》时也是这种感觉
I feel the same way when I watch "Empire."
不是吧你
Oh! No, you don't!
有只脏猫总是坐到我新买的劳斯莱斯顶上
Some mangy cat keeps sitting on the roof of my new Rolls.
梅尔夫收集名车
Merv collects cars.
不是我显摆  但我收集的车
Not to brag, but I could do a production
都够拍《十二怒汉》汽车版了
of "12 Angry Men" starring cars.
不是吧你  太妃喵
No, you don't, Taffy!
他的话是什么意思
What-What is he talking about?
感染麦德逊大道的热情是什么
What's Madison Avenue flu?
我好像跟他提过
Oh. I-I may have mentioned that you had a --
你对宣传推广行业萌生了兴趣
a budding interest in the promotional arts,
撞大运的是  梅尔夫的助手
and, total stroke of luck, Merv's assistant
得了很重很重的病
is very, very sick.
等等  你觉得我的事业
Wait a minute. You think my business
和"卡尔的改车行"马桶座圈
is in the same universe as
是同一个宇宙里吗
Carl's Auto Body toilet seat covers?
多亏那个宝贝的福
Carl just opened a third location
卡尔刚刚开了第三家分店了
because of that wizard.
你只剩两条命了  太妃喵
You got two lives left, Taffy!
你就打算这么用这两条命吗
Is this how you want to spend them?!
我不需要找工作  我已经有工作了
I don't need a job. I have one.
你不是"懂你"战队的吗
What happened to "Team Gets It"?
其实我不懂
Well, I don't gets it.
看起来你只是混在舞厅里
Just seems like you're hanging out at clubs
和一群派对女拍照而已
taking pictures with a bunch of party girls.
我也想当个潮爸
I mean, I want to be hip,
但我压根搞不懂这些是在干嘛
but none of this makes any sense to me.
我只是希望你能得到最好的
I just want what's best for you.
多谢"激励"  也多谢你小看我
Nice pep talk. Oh, and thanks for underestimating me.
爆米花大亨
如果你是奥威尔·瑞登巴克的爹
You know, if you were Orville Redenbacher's dad,
海莉把他和奥维尔·莱特搞混了
飞机永远不会被发明出来
we wouldn't have airplanes!
打败你了
Got ya!
看来九命怪猫也不代表就能次次命大
I guess they don't always land on their feet.
触地得分
Touchdown!
那个德怀特真是厉害
That Dwight's something, huh?
是啊  他还行吧
Yeah! Well, he's fine, you know.
这是项团体性运动
It's-It's a team sport,
他要是不在了大概都没人会想他
so, you know, they probably wouldn't even miss him.
我只想说一句
I just want to say
-我很欣赏您的选择  -谢谢
- I love what you're doing. - Well, thank you.
我都是用这种裤子来搭这件毛衣
I-I wear this sweater with these trousers a lot.
当你的腰部很高
When you're high-waisted,
要找到能相衬的上下身衣裤真的很难...
it is very difficult finding pieces that work together, so...
你的确看起来很时髦  但她的意思是
Yeah, you look really nice, but what she means is
您选择让德怀特住在你们家的举动很高尚
it's great that you're letting Dwight live with you.
你收留了德怀特吗
You're taking Dwight in?
-听起来不像你的作风啊  -这个
- That doesn't sound like you. - It's -- It's --
他要逼他搬出去
He's making him move out.
那听起来倒像你的作风
That sounds like you.
你们好  废柴们
Hey, losers.
我就感觉在小卖部[老人站牌]看到的是你
Thought I'd see you down at the concession stand.
你想了多久才想到这个双关语
How long were you working on that one?
这是你给卢克写的演讲稿里的笑话吗
Is that one of the gems that you wrote into Luke's speech?
我告诉你们  卢克的演讲稿是他自己写的
I will have you know that Luke wrote his own speech.
他参与了写作
He contributed.
他在场而已
He was there. Mm.
你这身西装是怎么回事
What's with the suit?
还说我  你为什么穿得跟女歌手麻辣鸡似的
Me? Why are you dressed like Nicki Minaj?
我妈和杰说这样会让我更能引起共鸣
My mom and Jay said it made me more relatable.
我觉得自己像个白痴一样
I feel like an idiot.
是啊  我也是
Yeah. Me too.
我妈逼我穿成这样  好让我更像你
My mom forced me to wear this so I'd be more like you.
说得好像我会用棕色皮带配黑皮鞋一样
Yeah, because I'd wear a brown belt with black shoes?
你知道我们该怎么做吗
You know what we should do?
弃稿  发自内心去演讲
Throw out our speeches and speak from the heart.
真是个好主意
That's a great idea.
你忘带演讲稿了是不是
Mm. You forgot your speech, didn't you?
应该是第五修正案  即不能自证其罪
我要行使第二修正案法
I plead the second.
另外你们该知道
Also, uh, You should know,
三个行凶者里已经有两个被抓到了
they arrested two of the three perpetrators.
宝贝  你来这做什么
Hey, honey. What are you doing here?
证明自己
Making a point.
你们好
Oh. Hey.
我是菲尔·邓菲
Uh, I-I'm Phil Dunphy.
有问题的话  尽管问
Feel free to ask any... questions.
脖子上的纹身不错
Sweet neck tattoo.
别忘了在访客登记簿上签名
Don't forget to sign the guest book.
这些不是你工作上的朋友吗
Aren't these your, uh -- your work friends?
没错  等一下
Yeah. Hold on a second.
亚利桑那  你又撅鸭子嘴了
Hey, Arizona! Quack quack.
抱歉
Sorry.
我知道你不认为我做的是正经工作
Look, I know you don't think what I'm doing is real,
但我们刚刚才通过我们在各个平台上的账号
but we just posted about this terrible house
发布了这间烂房子的出售信息
through all our accounts on multiple platforms,
现在慕名而来的人已经一大堆了
and there's already a ton of people here,
所以说  不用谢啦
so, uh, you're welcome.
我们真不需要搞这些  但好吧
We don't really need all this stuff, but okay.
好了  各位观众
All right, everybody.
在我们的仪仗队粉墨登场
Before our marching band takes the field
带来致敬扎克·埃夫隆系列电影的表演之前
with their tribute to the films of Zac Efron,
美国男演员  曾出演众多青春与歌舞电影
让我们有请两位候选人
let's hear from our two candidates
带来他们学生会主席的竞选演讲
for Student Council President.
首先出场的是曼尼·迪尔加多
First up is Manny Delgado.
实际上  我们打算一起完成这次演讲
Actually, we're going to speak together.
卢克和我站在这里  是希望赢得你们的投票
Luke and I are here because we each want your votes.
然而  某些人却一心想改变我们
However, certain people want to change us
让我们变得完全不像我们自己
into being something each of us is not.
-他们居然这样公开羞辱我们  -是我们自找的
- They're publicly shaming us. - We deserve it.
最重要的是你们两位家长学到教训
The important thing is you two learned something.
省省吧  大家长
Save it, patriarch.
我们想说的是  我们是两个
The point is, we are two individuals
拥有着截然不同的个性和想法的人
with our own unique personalties and ideas.
他说得没错
What he said.
最后我赢了
I won.
这次创了学校历史上最低的投票记录
It was the lowest voter turnout in school history.
选民讨厌我们俩个
They hated the both of us.
不过讨厌你更多一点
But you more.
我不得不承认  我确实有点佩服你真的带来了
I got to admit, I'm really impressed that you got
这么一大屋子人  不过他们...
all these people here, but they, um --
看起来不太像会买房子的人
they don't really look like house buyers.
爸  你完全不会看这年代的有钱人
Dad, you have no idea who has money anymore.
看到那个女孩了吗
You see that girl?
她靠玩电脑游戏就能赚进六位数
She makes six figures playing video games.
还有那个男的  他发明了一个应用
And that dude, he invented an app
专门用来吐槽朋友  叫做最佳"损"友
for trashing your friends called App Smear.
他们里面随便谁都买得起这房子
Oh. Any one of these people could buy this house.
而如果他们买下了  我们从你的佣金中抽头
And if they do, you give us a percentage of your commission.
这就是我们的生财之道
That's how we make money.
你是这个房子的中介吗
You the realtor?
正是在下
Indeed, I am.
我挺喜欢这里的
I like this place.
能指给我看看凶案发生的地方吗
Show me where it happened.
就在...这个走廊的尽头
Um, it's...right down this hall.
您先请
After you.
她爸爸可有钱了
Her dad's loaded.
顺便提一下  你看过房子的价格了吗
By the way, have you seen the price?
房东不是这里唯一被砍过的东西  还有房价
The, uh -- The owner wasn't the only thing that's been slashed.
海豚队获胜  21比20
And the Dolphins win, 21-20.
厉害了我的弟
All right!
那个男孩就像职业选手一样
That boy is like a professional.
一个男孩就差不多带整队赢了  太厉害了
It's amazing how one kid can carry a whole team.
我感觉你就是故意说给我听的
I feel like you're doing this on purpose.
打扰了  普里契特先生
Excuse me, Mr. Pritchett.
我是莱斯丽·关·柯林斯  《每日海豚报》的记者
Leslie Kwan Collins, Daily Dolphin.
因为如英雄般收留了德怀特这件事
For heroically taking in Dwight,
您被评为了本月的"海豚杰出人士"
you are this month's "Person with a Porpoise."
这我不敢当...
I don't know about that...
接受吧
Embrace it.
你跟我过来一下
Hey, come over here for just minute, buddy.
打得好  打得好
Good game! Good game.
-谢谢教练  -没事
- Thanks, Coach. - Yes.
听我说  我有一个你难以接受的事得告诉你
So, listen, I got something kind of rough I need to tell you.
我知道你跟米奇尔不只是室友那么简单
No, I know you and Mitchell aren't just roommates.
我对你的感恩之情难以言喻
I can't tell you how much I appreciate
你为我做的一切我十分感谢
everything you're doing for me.
听我说  我也不知道该怎么跟你开口
Yeah, listen, I don't know how I'm gonna tell you this.
所以我就不说了
So I'm not gonna.
我要你接下来按我说的每句话做
I just need you to do everything I tell you.
把你的头靠到我肩上
Put your head on my shoulder.
就是这样  靠上来
That's it. Get in there.
然后我要你假装你开始哭了
Now, I need you to pretend to start crying,
肩膀多放点感情
really get those shoulders into it.
没错  这样很棒
Yeah, that's it. That's good.
天啊  天啊  他告诉他了
Oh, God. Oh, God. He's telling him.
-别心软  -没错
- Stay strong. - Yes.
现在我要开始哭了  对不起
Now I'm gonna cry. I'm sorry!
我对不起你
I'm sorry!
好了  最后一步
Okay, final step --
你得坐下  抱住自己膝盖
I just need you to sit down, grab your knees,
然后边摇晃边难过  懂吗
and start rocking sadly, all right?
好了  坐下
All right, sit.
打扰一下  请大家听我说几句
Excuse me. Can I have everyone's attention, please?
想必大家都知道  德怀特的父亲最近被
As you know, uh, Dwight's father was recently restationed
调到佛罗里达驻扎  而我是一开始是想
to Florida and it was my intention to have my family
让德怀特到我家一起住  但不幸的是...
have Dwight live with us, but unfortunately --
不幸的是我们球队的对手啊
But unfortunately for our opponents,
他整季都会一直在队里
he's gonna be with us all season,
因为谣言说得没错
because the rumors are true.
德怀特会留下来
Dwight is going to be staying with us!
这真是最美好的善举了
That is the more beautiful gesture ever.
谢谢
Aww, thanks.
看来我的确到后来总是会想通啊
I guess I do always come around, huh?
是啊
Yes.
德怀特  你继续留下啊  怎么还难过
Dwight, you're staying. What -- What's going on?
我也不知道
I don't know.
教练让我坐下然后假装难过
Coach just told me to sit on the ground and look sad.
-小卡  -让我们为本月
Cam? Uh, let's hear it for this month's
"海豚杰出人士"米奇尔·普里契特欢呼
"Person with a Porpoise" -- Mitchell Pritchett!
等等  你怎么知道...
Wait. How -- How did you know about that --
那个记者是不是...
Did that reporter -- Oh!
等我回到家  咱们这事得认真谈谈
We are having a serious conversation when I get home.
但我好喜欢这感觉
But I'm loving this!
菲尔  你有何事所求
So, Phil, what can I do you for?
明智的大师
Well, oh wise one...
卢克现在是学生会主席了
...uh, Luke here is President of the Student Council,
但他需要专业人士的一些帮助
but he needs some professional help.
我不太讨人喜欢
I have a likability issue.
从你走进来的那一刻我就看出来了
Yeah, I saw that when you came in.
我们需要做的  就是好好推销你
What we need to do is promote you, okay?
我能看到"我爱卢克"别针
I see a pin, "I like Luke."
还有"卢克攻无不克"手环
I see a bracelet, "Luke is no fluke."
以及体育馆座椅靠垫"卢克在背后挺你"的画面
I see a stadium cushion, "Luke has your back...side."
你都怎么想出来的
How do you do that?
那手机壳怎么样
How about phone cases?
-手机壳啊  -大师对不起
- Phone cases? - I am so sorry.
亲爱的  这就是为什么大家不喜欢你
Sweetheart, this is why people don't like you.